{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What&#039;s the best selling video game to date?",
      "correct_answer": "Tetris",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Wii Sports", "Minecraft", "Super Mario Bros"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The main character in the &quot;Half-Life&quot; franchise is named Morgan Freeman.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What engine did the original &quot;Half-Life&quot; run on?",
      "correct_answer": "GoldSrc",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Source", "Quake", "Unreal"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which game did NOT get financed via Crowdfunding?",
      "correct_answer": "Enter the Gungeon",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Town of Salem", "Undertale", "Tower Unite"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What company created and developed the game &quot;Overwatch&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Blizzard Entertainment",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Valve", "Hi-Rez Studios", "Gearbox Software"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In &quot;Metal Gear Solid 2&quot;, you will see through the eyes of Psycho Mantis if you go first person during his boss fight.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is the leader of Team Mystic in Pok&eacute;mon Go?",
      "correct_answer": "Blanche",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Candela", "Spark", "Willow"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "What was the world&#039;s first handheld game device?",
      "correct_answer": "Mattel Auto Race",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Game Boy", "Microvision", "Game &amp; Watch"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "In the video game &quot;League of Legends&quot; which character is known as &quot;The Sinister Blade&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Katarina",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Shaco", "Akali", "Zed"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Valve&#039;s &quot;Portal&quot; and &quot;Half-Life&quot; franchises exist within the same in-game universe.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    }
  ]
}
